{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Heat Pump Installation Contractors","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40286/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40286,"taskName":"Heat Pump - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Heat Pump","xmTaskDescriptor":"Heat Pump Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":116,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"HVAC Heat Pump conditioning condition","textMessagingName":"Inst Heat Pump","rolloverLongDesc":"Uses the same technology as an air conditioner. Cools in summer \u0026 heats in winter. Has a unit that looks like the outside part of an air conditioner. Not as powerful a heater as gas forced air, but very energy efficient.","rolloverShortDesc":"Heats \u0026 cools. Has outside unit like air conditioner.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Heat Pump.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Heat Pump Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace a Heat Pump","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Heat Pump Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Heat Pump - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Heat Pump Project","urlName":"Heat-Pump-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Heat Pump Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"heat pump, geothermal heat pump, hvac, heating, cooling","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":587,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40286/":{"taskOID":40286,"originalTaskOID":40286,"setID":587,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4717,"questionDisplayText":"Install or Replace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you installing a new heat pump or replacing an old one?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installing new","answerDisplayText":"Installing new","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replacing old","answerDisplayText":"Replacing old","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4719,"questionDisplayText":"Heat pump type wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heat pump do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air source","answerDisplayText":"Air source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10095,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","answerDisplayText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water source","answerDisplayText":"Water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4718,"questionDisplayText":"Heating System Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the type of heating system you are using.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3118,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","answerDisplayText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3174,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3177,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2178,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric wall heater","answerDisplayText":"Electric wall heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4717,"questionDisplayText":"Install or Replace","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you installing a new heat pump or replacing an old one?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installing new","answerDisplayText":"Installing new","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replacing old","answerDisplayText":"Replacing old","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installing new","answerDisplayText":"Installing new","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5294,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replacing old","answerDisplayText":"Replacing old","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4719,"questionDisplayText":"Heat pump type wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heat pump do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air source","answerDisplayText":"Air source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10095,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","answerDisplayText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water source","answerDisplayText":"Water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":721,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air source","answerDisplayText":"Air source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10095,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","answerDisplayText":"Ground source (Geothermal)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water source","answerDisplayText":"Water source","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4718,"questionDisplayText":"Heating System Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the type of heating system you are using.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3118,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","answerDisplayText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3174,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3177,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2178,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric wall heater","answerDisplayText":"Electric wall heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Gas-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","answerDisplayText":"Electric-fired forced air (central heating)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3118,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","answerDisplayText":"Hydronic baseboard heat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3174,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat inside the floor - indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3177,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","answerDisplayText":"In-floor radiant - outdoors (walkways and driveways)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7092,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood stove","answerDisplayText":"Wood stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4635,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pellet stove","answerDisplayText":"Pellet stove","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2178,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Electric wall heater","answerDisplayText":"Electric wall heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}